AYOBAMI — ADEOLU

■ PRODUCT DESIGNER

+2347087980073 | sojiadeolu1@gmail.com

www.ayoadeolu.com

ABOUT

Product designer with 4+ years experience working as visual designer, branding expert and UI/UX Designer. I've had the privilege of working on creative teams for companies and start ups on freelance, remote and full time basis and I have carried out several projects on small and large scales.

I am a team player, I can leverage on proven achievements, working knowledge of design softwares and methodology to deliver professionally as expected.

SKILLS

Figma	Adobe XD	Keynote
Adobe Illustrator	Framer	Sketch
Photoshop	Invision	HTML/CSS

TRAINING/COURSES

UI/UX DESIGN FOUNDATION

STUTERN GRADUATE ACCELERATOR

COMPLETED

EDUCATION

Obafemi Awolowo University 2013 - 2018

■ BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Pure and Applied Chemistry

HOBBIES

Photography	Traveling	Movies
Music	Metaverse	Meditation

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2021 - Present

ARCHIBALD LONDON

UI/UX DESIGNER

- Work with engineering and product stakeholders to design, prototype and validate new and existing products
- Uphold standard design practices by creating and maintaining design systems and clearly communicating the rationale behind UX designs
- Executed user research and visual design for the e-commerce web and mobile app (iOS and Android).

Jun. 2019 - Dec. 2020

NATURES OWN WONDER

PRODUCT DESIGNER

- Wireframed user flows, user stories and user interfaces of several end-to-end mobile and web apps.
- Designed 2 fin-tech applications, 3 e-commerce marketplaces, 1 learning management systems, and over 12 corporate websites and landing pages.

Mar. 2019 - May 2019

SCELLOO - INTERNSHIP

UI/UX DESIGNER

- Arranged the end-to-end user research and user interface design of 3 flagship enterprise products as well as the company's 1st ever design system.
- Worked effectively with the design team towards the execution of user research, user testing and creation of wireframes, visual design, flows and prototypes for web and mobile apps.

Jan. 2019 - Mar 2021

VORTEX247

DIGITAL DESIGNER (FREELANCE)

- Handled the entire product lifecycle and management of Vortex247 mobile app
- Created websites using WordPress CMS and handled copywriting for landing pages, email newsletters, online advertisements, blog posts and search engine optimization.
- Reduced the company's marketing budget by 18% by creating and implementing growth hack strategies.